Guide to the Elizabeth Robins Papers 1803-1963 MSS 002
Fales Library and Special Collections
- Series VII: Literary Productions
  - Time is Whispering
    - Autumn, chapters 11-15 TS (Box 68, Folder 10)
    - Autumn, chapters 16-20 TS (Box 68, Folder 11)
    - Autumn, chapters 21-25 TS (Box 68, Folder 12)
    - Autumn, chapters 26-30 TS (Box 68, Folder 13)
    - Time is Whispering, chapters 1-7 TS (Box 68, Folder 14)
    - Time is Whispering, chapters 14-26 TS (Box 69, Folder 15)
    - Time is Whispering, chapters 27-32 TS (Box 69, Folder 16)
    - William Archer's criticisms, 1922 (Box 69, Folder 17)
    - Florence Bell's criticisms (Box 69, Folder 18)
  - Valentine Cobb, (1895)
    - Notes MS (Box 70, Folder 1)
    - Pages 1-222 MS (Box 70, Folder 2)
    - Pages 1-87 TS (Box 70, Folder 3)
    - Pages 88-196 TS (Box 70, Folder 4)
  - Votes for Women, (1906)
    - Friend of Women (original) MS (Box 71, Folder 1)
    - Friend of Women (final rough draft) MS (Box 71, Folder 2)
    - Friend of Women, Acts I and III (early version) TS (Box 71, Folder 3)
    - Votes for Women TS, 1909 (Box 71, Folder 4)
    - Notes from Henry James TS, 1906 (Box 71, Folder 5)
    - Votes for Women, Act I (four copies) TS (Box 71, Folder 6)
    - Votes for Women, Acts II and III TS (Box 71, Folder 7)
  - Way Stations
    - Time Tables or Commentaries MS (Box 72, Folder 1-3)
    - "The Suffrage Camp Revisited" TS (Box 72, Folder 4)
    - "At the Town Hall" MS (Box 72, Folder 5)
    - "Signs of the Times" TS (Box 72, Folder 6)
    - why?" MS (Box 72, Folder 7)
    - "Shall Women Work?" MS, TS (Box 72, Folder 8)
    - "Come and See" MS, TS (Box 72, Folder 9)
    - "Touchstones" MS (Box 72, Folder 10)
    - "Sermons in Stones" TS (Box 72, Folder 11)
    - Letters to the Times MS, reprints, 1911 -1912 (Box 72, Folder 12)
    - "Albert Hall, June 15, 1912" MS (Box 73, Folder 13)
    - "Under his Roof" MS (Box 73, Folder 14)
    - "Militant Tactics" MS, TS (Box 73, Folder 15)
    - Final article (untitled) MS (Box 73, Folder 16)
    - Fragments MS (Box 73, Folder 17)
    - TS (Box 73, Folder 18-19)
  - Where are You Going to?
    - Where are You Going To? MS (Box 74, Folder 1-2)
    - Where are You Going To? MS/TS (Box 74, Folder 3)
    - Where are You Going To? (with notes) TS (Box 74, Folder 4)
    - Where are You Going To? TS (Box 74, Folder 5)
    - Where are You Going To?/My Little Sister MS (Notes) (Box 74, Folder 6)
    - Where are You Going To? Notes, clippings MS (Box 74, Folder 7)
    - My Little Sister, Act I MS/TS (Box 75, Folder 8)
    - My Little Sister, Act II MS/TS (Box 75, Folder 9)
    - My Little Sister, Act III MS/TS (Box 75, Folder 10)
    - My Little Sister, Act IV MS/TS (Box 75, Folder 11)
    - My Little Sister, Act I TS (Box 75, Folder 12)
    - My Little Sister, Act II TS (Box 75, Folder 13)
    - My Little Sister, Act III TS (Box 75, Folder 14)
    - My Little Sister, Act IV TS (Box 75, Folder 15)
    - Correspondence, 1913 -1944 (Box 75, Folder 16)
      Includes William Archer, Actresses' Franchise League, Woman's Theatre, ER letters.
    - Correspondence re: Annie Vivanti's alleged plagiarism of Where are You Going To?, 1920 -1921 (Box 75, Folder 17)
  - White Violets or Great Powers
    - Great Powers, chapters 1-10 MS (Box 76, Folder 1)
    - Great Powers, chapters 11-17 MS (Box 76, Folder 2)
    - White Violets, chapters 1-5, 18-20 MS (Box 76, Folder 3)
    - White Violets, odd chapters MS (Box 76, Folder 4)
    - White Violets, notes MS (Box 76, Folder 5)
    - White Violets, chapter 1 TS (Box 76, Folder 6)
    - White Violets, chapters 1-15 TS (Box 76, Folder 7)
    - White Violets, chapters 16-26 TS (Box 76, Folder 8)
    - White Violets, chapters 1-15 TS (Box 77, Folder 9)
    - White Violets, chapters 16-26 TS (Box 77, Folder 10)
    - White Violets, odd chapters TS (Box 77, Folder 11)
  - Whither and How, (1891)
    - Introductory TS (Box 78, Folder 1)
    - Chapter 1 MS, TS (Box 78, Folder 2)
    - Chapter 2 MS/TS (Box 78, Folder 3)
    - Chapters 1-6 TS (Box 78, Folder 4)
    - Chapters 7-15 TS (Box 78, Folder 5)
    - Chapters 37-39 TS (Box 78, Folder 6)
    - Chapters 40-49 TS (Box 78, Folder 7)
    - Chapter 50 TS (Box 78, Folder 8)
    - Notes "odd bits" TS (Box 78, Folder 9)
    - Notes "In case a vol. III" MS (Box 78, Folder 10)
  - Additional Titles
    - The Alaska Boundary TS (Box 79, Folder 1)
    - Among My Books; The British Merlin MS (Box 79, Folder 2)
    - Anglo-American Understanding. A Talk with Mr. Otto Kahn MS (Box 79, Folder 3)
    - Bret Harte and Madame Van de Velde TS (Box 79, Folder 4)
    - The Caribou Stand MS (Box 79, Folder 5)
    - The Caribou Stand TS (Box 79, Folder 6)
    - The Caribou Stand TS (Box 79, Folder 7)
    - Catching the Train for America (Box 79, Folder 8)
    - The Centaur TS (Box 79, Folder 9)
    - Christabel MS (Box 79, Folder 10)
    - Christabel TS (Box 79, Folder 11)
    - Christabel Pankhurst and White Slavery, or The Girl with the Lamp MS (Box 79, Folder 12)
    - Christabel Pankhurst and White Slavery, or The Girl with the Lamp TS (Box 79, Folder 13)
    - Clare and Jerry TS (Box 79, Folder 14)
      A Close Up View of Queen Victoria and the English Stage--see An American Actress at Balmoral Castle.
    - The Coming Woman, or The Leading Lady, pages 1-45 TS (Box 79, Folder 15)
    - The Coming Woman, or the Leading Lady, pages 46-117 TS (Box 79, Folder 16)
    - The Coming Woman, or the Leading Lady, pages 1-66 TS (Box 79, Folder 17)
    - Current Ideas, speech before the Pioneer Club, Brighton, 1919 (Box 79, Folder 18)
    - The Derrington Ghost (Box 79, Folder 19)
    - Diana and Natur Heil MS (Box 79, Folder 19A)
    - An Education Act (Box 79, Folder 20)
    - Edward VIII (Box 80, Folder 21)
    - An Egyptian Necklace (Box 80, Folder 22)
    - The Father of Lies MS, 1895 (Box 80, Folder 23)
    - The Father of Lies TS (Box 80, Folder 24)
    - The Father of Lies, fragment TS (carbon) (Box 80, Folder 25)
    - Gertrude Bell--radio broadcast, September 1927 MS (Box 80, Folder 26)
      See also Box 83, Folder 64.
    - Gertrude Bell--radio broadcast, September 1927 (3 copies) TS (Box 80, Folder 27)
    - Gertrude Bell--radio broadcast, correspondence and newspaper clippings (Box 80, Folder 28)
    - Gertrude Lowthian Bell (Box 80, Folder 29)
    - Grey, Dorothy [obituary] (Box 80, Folder 30)
    - Heights and Depths TS (Box 80, Folder 31)
    - Henrik Ibsen: The Drama of Ideas, A Determined Originator (Box 80, Folder 32)
    - Him and Her MS (Box 80, Folder 33)
    - Ibsen--BBC talk given March 19, 1928 TS (Box 80, Folder 34)
    - Ibsen and the Actress (Box 80, Folder 35)
    - An Impression of Sarah Bernhardt's Hamlet MS (Box 80, Folder 36)
    - An Incident of Travel (includes a page by William Archer) MS (Box 80, Folder 37)
    - Jassamine Gardens (Box 80, Folder 38)
    - Judith, Act I MS, 1906 (Box 80, Folder 39)
    - Judith, Act II MS (Box 80, Folder 40)
    - Judith, notes MS (Box 80, Folder 41)
    - Kaiomi TS (Box 80, Folder 42)
    - Katherine Fleets (fragment) MS (Box 80, Folder 43)
    - Lady Quassia MS (Box 80, Folder 44)
    - Letters to the Editor MS/TS, 1898 -1939 (Box 80, Folder 45)
    - A Lost Opportunity (Box 80, Folder 46)
    - The Main Peace Asset MS (Box 80, Folder 47)
    - A Masterpiece the World Never Saw, or Aphrodite of the West TS (Box 80, Folder 48)
    - Miss Cal (or Suffrage, Looking Back) MS/TS (Box 81, Folder 49)
    - Miss de Maupassant MS (Box 81, Folder 50)
    - Miss de Maupassant TS (Box 81, Folder 51)
    - A Modern Woman, Born 1689 (An Impression of Lady Mary) MS (Box 81, Folder 52)
    - Monica's Village MS (Box 81, Folder 53)
    - Monica's Village TS (Box 81, Folder 54)
    - Monica's Village, "cut (for reading aloud) Jan. 1910" TS (Box 81, Folder 55)
    - Newtimber Tale MS, notes (Box 81, Folder 56)
    - The Old England and the New TS (Box 81, Folder 57)
      See also "The Spirit of the People" in Box 82, Folders 74 and 75 and "To the Homekeepers of America" in Box 82, Folder 79.
    - The Old Woman of the Sea (play fragment) TS (Box 81, Folder 58)
    - On Tour, or Across the Continent with Junius Brutus Booth MS (Box 81, Folder 59)
    - On Tour, or Across the Continent with Junius Brutus Booth TS (Box 81, Folder 60)
    - Oscar Wilde TS (Box 81, Folder 61)
    - Oscar Wilde, notes MS (Box 81, Folder 62)
    - Pengarnack's Necklace, by ER, condensed by William Archer TS, MS (Box 81, Folder 63)
    - Pleasure Mining MS (Box 81, Folder 64)
    - Pleasure Mining TS (Box 81, Folder 65)
    - Poppy and Mandragora, unfinished MS, 1894 (Box 81, Folder 66)
    - Reaction MS (Box 81, Folder 67)
      See also "Temptation" in Box 82, Folder 78 and "She Loves to Sew" in Box 81, Folder 69.
    - A Separable Friend MS (Box 81, Folder 68)
    - She Loves to Sew MS (Box 81, Folder 69)
      See also "Reaction" in Box 81, Folder 67 and "Temptation" in Box 82, Folder 78.
    - Sixes and Sevens MS (Box 81, Folder 70)
    - Sixes and Sevens TS (Box 81, Folder 71)
    - Some Aspects of Henrik Ibsen TS (Box 82, Folder 72)
    - Some Aspects of Henrik Ibsen-lecture delivered before the Philosophical Institute, Edinburgh. October 27, 1908 TS (Box 82, Folder 73)
    - The Spirit of the People TS, carbon (Box 82, Folder 74)
      See also "To the Homekeepers of America" in Box 82, Folder 79 and "The Old England and the New" in Box 81, Folder 57.
    - The Spirit of the People (incl. fragments) TS (Box 82, Folder 75)
    - Stall B. 25 (Box 82, Folder 76)
    - Suffrage (Box 82, Folder 77)
    - Temptation (Box 82, Folder 78)
      See also "Reaction" in Box 82, Folder 67 and "She Loves to Sew" in Box 82, Folder 69.
    - To the Home Keepers in America from the Home Keepers in England TS (Box 82, Folder 79)
      See also "The Old England and the New" in Box 81, Folder 57 and "The Spirit of the People" in Box 82, Folders 74 and 75.
    - Under the Southern Cross, or The Peruvian MS (Box 82, Folder 80)
    - Under the Southern Cross TS (Box 82, Folder 81)
      See also Box 83, Folder 66.
    - Woman's Secret (Box 82, Folder 82)
      See also Oversize Material, Box 3, Folder 3.
    - Unidentified manuscript (Box 82, Folder 83)
    - Unidentified manuscript ("Antidote") (Box 82, Folder 84)
    - Unidentified manuscript (Box 82, Folder 84A)
    - Unidentified manuscript (Box 82, Folder 84B)
    - Unidentified manuscript (speech at Rounton Grange) (Box 82, Folder 84C)
    - Unidentified typescript (Box 82, Folder 85-88)
  - Additional Titles: Legal Size Material
    - Gertrude Bell (Box 83, Folder 64)
    - Paternalism (Box 83, Folder 65)
      See also Series Two, Subseries B, Box 20, Folder 150: "Rhondda."
    - Under the Southern Cross (Box 83, Folder 66)
    - Unidentified MS (Box 83, Folder 67)
  - Sources for Literary Productions
    - Ancilla's Share, "Notes on books read for Ancilla days" (Box 84, Folder 1)
    - Ancilla's Share - sources (Box 84, Folder 2)
    - Anti-war notes (Box 84, Folder 3)
    - Attempted Precise of E.M.F.'s Lecture of V.W. (Box 84, Folder 4)
    - [Both Sides of the Curtain(?)], "First Summary for Own Book" (Box 84, Folder 5)
    - The Children (Box 84, Folder 6)
    - Chinsegut and Aunt Jane Cole, notes (Box 84, Folder 7)
    - "Diary Notes" (Box 84, Folder 8)
    - Goin' t'a Cane-Grindin' (Box 84, Folder 9)
    - Hall Caine (notes on interview with) (Box 84, Folder 10)
    - Horde MS (1 of 3) (Box 84, Folder 11)
    - Horde MS (2 of 3) (Box 84, Folder 12)
    - Horde MS (3 of 3) (Box 84, Folder 13)
    - Horde "Mixed Lot" (Box 84, Folder 14)
    - Horde "Before Democracy" (Box 84, Folder 15)
    - Horde "Pilgrimage" (Box 84, Folder 16)
    - Horde (Box 84, Folder 17)
    - James McNeill Whistler (Box 84, Folder 17A)
    - Lisbon notes (Box 84, Folder 18)
    - Margot Asquith, notes (Box 84, Folder 19)
    - "Miss Patching" (Box 84, Folder 20)
    - A Portrait [Mr. and Mrs. Yates Thompson] (Box 84, Folder 21)
    - People notes, for autobiography (Box 85, Folder 22)
    - People notes, for autobiography (Box 85, Folder 23)
    - Race Relations, notes (Box 85, Folder 24)
      See also Series XII: Printed Materialm.
    - Raymond and I (Box 85, Folder 24A)
    - Stead, William T. (Box 85, Folder 25)
    - Suffrage -- notes and transcripts, 1906 (Box 85, Folder 26)
    - The Theatre (Box 85, Folder 27)
    - [untitled], fragment, "I think this is the story of the woman carver I saw in York" (Box 85, Folder 28)
    - Vernon [Robins] notes (Box 86, Folder 29)
    - War time notes (Box 86, Folder 30)
    - [Where are You Going To?(?)] sources (Box 86, Folder 31-41)
    - Unidentified notes (Box 87, Folder 42-55)
    - Unidentified notes (Box 88, Folder 56-63)
- Series VIII: Theater Productions
  Series VIII reflects Elizabeth Robins's interest in non-profit theater and Ibsen dramas. With the exception of the acting contracts dating from 1883, when Robins was living in America, and a prompt copy for The King's Pleasure, the materials in this series relate to her theater experiences in England. In addition, there is material relating to the production of Votes for Women!, Robins's suffrage play, published in 1907.
  - Subseries A: Business Records
    Subseries A contains business records from the period when Robins produced and/or acted in such Ibsen plays as Hedda Gabler (1891, 1898), The Master Builder (1893), and Little Eyolf (1896). There are also business accounts and seating charts for the 1897 production of Echegaray's Mariana, which she directed. Some of these plays were produced by the New Century Theatre, which Robins, William Archer, and others formed.
    - Hedda Gabler 1891, 1898 (Box 1, Folder 1)
      See also Oversize Material, Box 4, Folder 2.
    - Ibsen Performances at the Opera Comique Theatre 1893 (Box 1, Folder 2)
      See also individual plays.
    - Ibsen subscription performances 1894 (Box 1, Folder 3)
    - Ibsen birthday subscriptions 1898 (Box 1, Folder 4)
    - Karin (May-June) 1892 (Box 1, Folder 5)
    - Little Eyolf 1896 (Box 1, Folder 6)
      See also Oversize Material, Box 4, Folder 3.
    - Little Eyolf--ticket requests (November) 1896 (Box 1, Folder 7)
    - Mariana 1897 (Box 1, Folder 8)
      See also Oversize Material, Box 4, Folder 4.
    - The Master Builder 1893, 1895 (Box 1, Folder 9)
      See also Oversize Material, Box 4, Folder 5.
    - The Master Builder--set sketches, property list, names of actors suggested for play (Box 1, Folder 10)
    - The New Century Theatre 1897, n.d. (Box 1, Folder 11)
      See also Oversize Material, Box 13, Folder 10 and Series Two, Box 7: "Wm. Archer."
    - Votes for Women--correspondence re: production 1906, 1907 (Box 1, Folder 12)
    - Votes for Women--contract for production 1906 (Box 1, Folder 13)
    - Miscellaneous business records (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Subseries B: Prompt Copies and Annotated Typescripts
    Subseries B is made up of typescripts and prompt copies of Ibsen and Echegaray plays. Most are annotated by Robins and some contain other annotations: the typescript for Mariana has added corrections by both Henry James and William Archer. There are also a prompt copies of Mrs. Humphry Ward's Eleanor and of Henry James's play, The American, also annotated by Robins.
    - The American Printed (Box 2, Folder 1)
    - Eleanor (by Mary Augusta Ward) Printed (Box 2, Folder 2)
    - Hedda Gabler TS (Box 2, Folder 3)
    - Hedda Gabler, "Property of Elizabeth Robins and Marion Lea" TS (Box 2, Folder 4)
    - Hedda Gabler Printed (Box 2, Folder 5)
    - Hedda Gabler Printed (Box 2, Folder 6)
    - John Gabriel Borkman Printed (Box 2, Folder 7)
    - The King's Pleasure MS (Box 2, Folder 8)
    - Mariana (with corrections by Henry James and William Archer) TS (Box 2, Folder 9)
    - Mariana TS (Box 2, Folder 10)
    - Mariana TS (Box 2, Folder 11)
    - The Master Builder Printed (Box 3, Folder 12)
    - The Master Builder Printed (Box 3, Folder 13)
    - Queen Mary: Tragedy in 5 Acts TS/Printed (Box 3, Folder 14)
    - Rosmersholm (1886) Printed, 1896 (Box 3, Folder 15)
    - Votes for Women TS (bound) (Box 3, Folder 16)
    - The Witness (Pauline) TS, 1899 (Box 3, Folder 17)
- Series IX: Photographic Material
  All photographic materials from the Elizabeth Robins Papers are gathered together in Series Nine. Photographs which originated in other series, e.g. Series Two: General Correspondence, are marked appropriately. The photographs are arranged by subseries in albums, followed by boxes of over 5"x7," which correspond to each subseries. Larger oversize photographs are housed with Oversize Material.
  - Subseries A: Elizabeth Robins
    Subseries A contains photographs of Elizabeth Robins. Cabinet photos of her in American and English theatrical performances are arranged by title. There are also over forty formal portraits of Robins, varying from studio to passport photographs. Photos of Robins can also be found in Subseries C-F.
    - The American (Album 1, Photograph 1-9)
      See also Oversize Material, Box 8, Folder 1.
    - American King
      See Album 14, #129.
    - Divorce (Album 1, Photograph 10-24)
      See also Album 14, #130.
    - Dr. Bill (Album 1, Photograph 25)
    - Eleanor (Album 1, Photograph 26-29)
    - Forgiven (Album 1, Photograph 30)
    - Her Own Witness (Album 1, Photograph 31)
    - Little Lord Fauntleroy (Album 1, Photograph 32-38)
    - The Master Builder (Album 1, Photograph 39-51)
      See also Album 14, #131-133.
    - Mrs. Lessingham (Album 1, Photograph 52-60)
    - The Trumpet Call, 1891? (Album 1, Photograph 61-71)
    - Elizabeth Robins [ER] portraits (Album 1, Photograph 72-79)
    - Elizabeth Robins and Marion Lea (Album 1, Photograph 80)
    - ER portraits (Album 2)
      See aso Album 14, #134-163.
    - Group shots which include ER (Album 2, Photograph 6)
  - Subseries B: General Portraits
    Subseries B contains photographs of early American and British actors and actresses, many in costume and theatrical pose, along with portraits of Elizabeth Robins's friends (including classmates) and relatives. Photographs of Robins' husband, George Richmond Parks, an actor with the Boston Museum Company, are also included here, as well as cabinet photos of many of her theatrical colleagues. William Archer, Florence Bell and family, and Octavia Wilberforce all are substantially represented.
    - Ainley, Henry, 1902 (Album 2, Photograph 1)
    - Alexandra, Princess of Wales (Album 2, Photograph 2)
    - Ameen, Elin (Album 2, Photograph 3-4)
    - Amran, Isaac Ben, 1909 (Album 2, Photograph 5)
    - Anderson, Mary (Album 2, Photograph 6-8)
    - Archer, William (Album 2, Photograph 9)
    - Archer, William, 1891 (Album 2, Photograph 10-11)
    - Archer, William (Album 2, Photograph 12-13)
    - Archer, William, 1899 (Album 2, Photograph 14)
    - Archer, William (Album 2, Photograph 14A)
      See also Album 15, #352-53.
    - Aswell, Lena (Album 2)
    - Bacus, George A. (Album 2, Photograph 15)
    - Bacus, George A., 1883 (Album 2, Photograph 16)
    - Baird, Dorothea (Album 2)
      See Album 15, #355-56.
    - Baker, Clara (Album 2, Photograph 17-18)
    - Baleman, 1892 (Album 2, Photograph 19)
    - Barrett, Lawrence (Album 2, Photograph 20)
      See Album 15, #357.
    - Barron, Charles (Album 2, Photograph 21)
    - Bayley, Katherine (Album 2)
      See Album 15, #358.
    - Becker, Danforth, 1881 (Album 2, Photograph 22)
    - Bell, Elsa and Molly (Album 2, Photograph 23-24)
    - Bell, Florence and granddaughter Nora Richmond (Album 2, Photograph 25)
    - Bell, Florence (Album 2)
      See Album 15, #359-60.
    - Bell, Gertrude and Col. T. E. Lawrence (Album 2, Photograph 26)
    - Bell, Hugh (Album 2, Photograph 26)
      See Album 15, #361-62.
    - Bell, Hugo (Album 2, Photograph 27-28)
    - Bell, Molly (Album 2, Photograph 29)
    - Bell, Elsa (Album 2, Photograph 30)
    - Bell, Hugo (Album 2, Photograph 32)
    - Bell, Hugh and grandchild (Album 2, Photograph 32A)
    - Bell, Hugh and grandson (Album 2, Photograph 32-35)
    - Bell, Frances and sons (Album 2, Photograph 36-39)
    - Bells and Trevelyans (Album 2, Photograph 40)
    - Bell grandchildren (Album 2, Photograph 41)
    - Burstadt, A. (Album 2, Photograph 42)
    - Benson (aunt) (Album 2, Photograph 43)
    - Beringer, Esme (Album 2)
      See Album 15, #363.
    - Berringer, Vera (Album 2, Photograph 44)
    - Black, Dora and Emma Blandy (Album 2)
      See Album 15, #364.
    - Blackeston, Mrs. Clarence (Album 2, Photograph 45)
    - Blanchard, Gertie A., 1884 (Album 2, Photograph 46)
    - Blandy, Emma (Album 2, Photograph 47)
    - Blandy, Emma, 1881 (Album 2, Photograph 48-49)
    - Blandy, Emma, 1883 (Album 2, Photograph 50)
    - Blandy, Emma, 1886 (Album 2, Photograph 51)
    - Blandy, Emma, 1889 (Album 2, Photograph 52)
    - Blandy, Emma (Album 2, Photograph 53)
    - Blandy, Emma, 1882 (Album 2, Photograph 54)
    - Blandy, Emma and Dora Black (Album 2, Photograph 54)
    - Blandy, Julia (Album 2, Photograph 55)
    - Blandy, Julia, 1880 (Album 2, Photograph 56)
    - Bloodgood, Clara S., 1899 (Album 2, Photograph 57)
    - Bodine, J.M. (Album 2, Photograph 58-63)
    - Bodine, Elizabeth (Album 2, Photograph 64-66)
    - Bodine, Lizzie (Mrs. McKay) and daughter Mary Bodine McKay, 1880 (Album 2, Photograph 67)
    - Bodine, Mary (Album 2, Photograph 68)
    - Boston Museum Company cast, 1884 Image 1. (Album 2, Photograph 69)
    - Boston Museum Company cast, 1884 Image 2. (Album 2, Photograph 70)
    - Breckenridge, Louise Tevis, 1883 (Album 2, Photograph 71)
    - Brough, Fanny (Album 2, Photograph 72)
    - Brough, Lionel (Album 2, Photograph 72)
      See Album 15, #365.
    - Browning, Elizabeth Barrett (Album 2, Photograph 73)
    - Buck, Mamie E., 1880 (Album 2, Photograph 74)
    - Buck, Charlie (Album 3, Photograph 75)
    - Buckingham, Julia (Album 3, Photograph 76)
    - Buckingham, Nellie and Bessie Guthrie (Album 3)
      See Album 19, #3.
    - Bull, Ole (Album 3, Photograph 77)
      See also Album 15, #366.
    - Bullitt, Annie (Album 3, Photograph 78)
    - Bullitt, Edith (Album 3, Photograph 79-83)
    - Bullitt, Edith and Bettie McGoodwin, 1879 (Album 3, Photograph 84)
    - Bullitt, Edith (Album 3, Photograph 85)
    - Bullitt, Edward (Album 3, Photograph 86-88)
    - Bullitt, Julia (Album 3, Photograph 89-90)
    - Bullitt, Lizzie (Album 3, Photograph 91)
    - Buxton (Album 3, Photograph 92)
    - Cable, George W. (Album 3, Photograph 93)
    - Caldwell, Marianne (Album 3, Photograph 94)
    - Calhoun, Nellie (Album 3, Photograph 95)
    - Campbell, Beatrice Stella (Album 3, Photograph 96-97)
    - Campbell, Beatrice Stella (Album 3, Photograph 98)
    - Campbell, Beatrice Stella (Album 3, Photograph 99)
    - Campbell, Beatrice Stella (Album 3, Photograph 100)
    - Campbell, Beatrice Stella (Album 3)
      See Album 15, #367.
    - Campbell, Beatrice Stella and Mr. Forbes Robinson (Album 3)
      See Album 15, #368.
    - Carlyle, Thomas (Album 3, Photograph 101)
    - Carrington, Emma Blandy (Album 3, Photograph 102)
    - Casson, Louis and Sybil and family, ca. 1933 (Album 3, Photograph 103)
    - Clarke, Annie M., 1885 (Album 3, Photograph 104)
    - Clemens, Samuel (Album 3, Photograph 105)
    - Clement, Hope (Album 3, Photograph 106-108)
    - Clifford, Lucy (Album 3, Photograph 109)
    - Coghlan, Charles (Album 3, Photograph 110)
    - Cooper, Peter (Album 3, Photograph 111)
    - Cordes, Albert (Album 3)
      See Album 19, #2.
    - Crackenthorpe, Mrs. (B.A.C.) (Album 3, Photograph 112)
    - Craik, Rev. James (Album 3, Photograph 113)
    - Crow, Edward, Jr. (Album 3)
      See Album 20, #1.
    - Cushman, Charlotte (Album 3, Photograph 114)
    - Cutter, Anna W. (Album 3, Photograph 115)
    - Cutter, Mrs. Chester and Nina (Album 3)
      See Album 15, #369.
    - Cutter, Chester G., 1883 (Album 3, Photograph 116)
    - Cutter, Fannie, 1883 (Album 3, Photograph 117)